

iuri.is depaula.iuri@gmail.com +55 14 99741-6590 Marília, Brazil

**Creative Frontend Developer** 

#### **Profile**

I am a front-end developer with more than 10 years of web development experience, lately working with Vue.js/React, Webpack, HTML, CSS and GSAP.

In the past years, at **biz** (A SaaS e-commerce platform), I was involved on many different projects, including frontend tools, micro-services, modules for Magento, APIs, and countless themes for e-commerce stores and services. Always with a focus on rapid deployment, easy maintenance, performance and achieving high results.

#### Main skills

JavaScript

· CSS

· HTML

Vue.js

Vue Router

Vuex

GSAP

Webpack

¡Query

Github

UX/UI

Design

Animation

SASS

• CSS-BEM

Agile

Scrum

· Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe XDWordPress

Magento

REST APIsAJAX

JSON

• E-commerce

Strategic Thinking

Storytelling

## **Experience**

## · Head of Product Design

at Biz Commerce, 2016 - 2019

We delivered more than 200 different products and projects, using Scrum and Agile methodologies with an emphasis on rapid deployment, easy maintenance, and performance. Increasing our customers sales with a fast and reliable platform and our partners quality and trust with robust solutions for payment and shipping services. Today we are running on 600+ stores, payment/shipping services and thousands of transactions every day.

#### · Head of UX/UI

at Biz Commerce, 2011 - 2016

I've led our team in creating and enhancing interfaces, navigation funnels, information architecture, legacy code optimization, code performance, SEO, and accessibility. In addition, we created new tools for our internal teams, which increased our customers' satisfaction and made our lives easier when managing projects.

Co-founded Biz Commerce ★

november, 2011

#### Head of Design & Frontend

at JOE. 2010 - 2014

We were a web studio/software house with one foothold on advertising.

I managed the creation of web applications, online magazines, news portals, and professional blogs. Some of our clients became some of the biggest names in Brazilian web and/or world wide, like <u>Porta dos Fundos</u> which became one of the greatest YouTube humor channels.

#### Co-founded JOE ★

march, 2010

## Senior Frontend Developer

at Tray, 2008 - 2010

My role was optimize the current interface codes, bringing the system to more modern technologies. Using jQuery and AJAX, and introducing responsive design practices.

I was also responsible for creating the visual identity for new products and for the company as a whole.

#### Web Designer

at E2W, 2006 - 2008

E2W (*E-commerce to World*) was an e-commerce group that managed everything from logistics to marketing campaigns for its stores. During the time I worked there, Red Nose, *Klikshop*, *Esporte Line*, and others brands were part of the group. I was responsible for creating banners, hot sites, ads, layouts for the stores, email marketing and branding campaigns.

## **Education**

#### **Bachelor of Philosophy**

UNESP, 2005

#### Languages

# Fluent

- Enalish
- Portuguese

## Intermediate

Spanish

#### Basic

- Catalan
- Japanese